I already have my answer.
I'm not second-guessing myself.
I think I'm coming to realize what limits you were talking about.
Then choose me.
Ichinose manages to act like the mature adult for you, huh?
I'll prove to you some things won't ever change.
I could continue pining for Ren,
and keep piling on reasons to love him.
But it would only hurt in the end.
Thanks for all you've done for me.
Hello?
Mayuka.
What's up?
They repainted the walls of my old apartment.
This bench has changed, too.
Plenty of things will remain the same though.
Ren, I'm going to say something that sounds crazy, okay?
I don't feel so bothered about my dad remarrying anymore.
So I'm okay now.
What are you leading up to?
Are we breaking up?
Bingo.
I don't get it.
Why?
You know...
I always thought you'd leave me behind one day.
I thought I needed to pick up something for myself
so I could stay at your side.
That's why I began modeling.
And yet, now this job has become really important to me.
A job I might prioritize over you.
Is that your reason?
- In that case -
- Besides...
If we accept the changes I go through,
then we have to accept your changes, too.
Ren.
I know there's already someone else in your heart.
Don't force yourself to forget and move on.
What do you mean, "force myself"?
Am I wrong for putting in the necessary effort
to keep our relationship thriving?
You were putting in an effort to keep your promise to me.
It wasn't for the sake of our relationship.
You'll always feel obligated in one way or another
if you stay with me.
That's just how it is.
- I don't -
- It'd only hurt me to see you like that, Ren.
If your feelings for me weren't ever a lie,
then I can't ask for anything more.
I've chosen to accept my changes.
You need to accept yours, too.
No feelings last forever, do they?
It's okay.
I'll always be here for you.
Always.
I'll be okay.
And I'm sure you will be, too.
Ren.
Bye-bye.
You're probably right, Ando. Pining for Ren will only hurt.
But I don't want to deny my feelings.
I want to stay in love with Ren.
I can't go out with you, while having feelings for someone else.
Ninako.
I love you.
I love you, even when you're rejecting me.
I really, really love you.
Remember when you said I'd get it
when I had a crush like yours?
Well, this is that crush.
So it doesn't look like I'll be able to move on any time soon.
Welcome home.
What happened?
I went and made the mature choice.
Guess I'll be seeing more honest smiles from you, huh?
Yeah, I think you will.
And the fact that I've come to terms with it,
means I've out-matured him.
Here, your make up is smearing.
There, there.
I wanted to grow up into adults with him.
- Daiki.
- Yeah?
Make sure you grow up with your girlfriend, okay?
Yeah, we will.
Alright, worry about yourself first, Sis.
There, there. You did great.
Liking someone is such a simple emotion.
Why does it become so complicated when that turns to love?
What?
They broke up? Why?
Daiki didn't know the exact reason either.
[Finale]
Ninako. This is your chance.
I don't think now is the time.
Ren is probably hurting a lot right now.
I wouldn't want to burden him with my feelings
when he's going through a rough spot.
I see.
Happy new year, Director!
- How's it going?
- Sorry to call you out here like this, Ren.
What did you need from me?
To tell you the truth, I like you.
Will you please go out with me?
I'm sorry.
Dating is the last thing on my mind right now.
No matter why they broke up, they were special to each other.
There's no way he's taking this okay.
Director?
You there, Director?
Caught you.
Sorry I spooked you.
Yeah, you sure did.
Hey, so...
I promise I wasn't trying to eavesdrop, okay?
I know.
See you around.
Yeah, see you.
Ninako, are you giving anyone chocolates for Valentine's Day?
Nope. No chocolates for friends, or crushes this year.
Really?
Aw, too bad.
How do you think I can get Ninako to crush on Ren again?
Beats me.
It really doesn't seem like she'll confess any time soon.
She's not even giving out chocolates for Valentine's this year.
But I think -
Ninako said that? Word for word?
Yeah.
Were you expecting to get something from her as a friend?
I was, yeah.
Hotshot.
I'm heading back out.
Sure, meet you there.
Score.
Ninako!
Happy Valentine's Day.
- What's this?
- Chocolate, obviously.
There's no rule saying guys can't give out chocolates, right?
Sorry, I can't accept this one.
I knew you'd say that.
That's why I prepared another version for you.
Chocolates for a friend, from a friend.
That's acceptable, right?
They're exactly the same.
Are you sure this is "for a friend"?
Duh, of course.
In return, I'll accept any candy "from a friend" for White Day.
Toodles.
What's the difference between chocolate for friends,
and for a crush?
Ninako!
- Morning!
- Morning.
- Say.
- Yeah?
Did you bring any chocolate today?
Specifically, for Ren.
Nope.
Aw, why not? Just give him something "as friends".
I didn't bring anything to give.
Liar, you always have snacks on you.
See?
I can say it's "from a friend",
but it'd really mean something more.
That's why I can't give him anything. At least, not this year.
Take your time, and he might find another girl, you know?
Exactly.
I forgot my English textbook.
Either of you got some chocolate to spare?
- Anyone?
- Gacchan.
Could I borrow your English textbook?
Sure, give me a second.
I forgot I brought mine home yesterday.
Ren.
Could Ninako borrow your English textbook?
Sure.
Here.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Here.
Thanks for letting me borrow your textbook.
Sure.
As thanks...
I'll let you borrow my textbook if you ever forget yours.
I'd appreciate that.
See you around.
See you.
Director?
You can't be wandering into the nurse's office.
Since today's Valentine's Day,
I've got a special treat, just for...
[No feeding the stray cat food]
No...
But I was just getting on Director's good side.
Eh, Mr. Hoshina wouldn't mind.
This is our secret, okay?
Look who I caught up to no good.
I'm telling all the teachers about you.
Rebelling against the Principal? You've got guts.
This isn't "food", it's a meal. I'm still in the clear.
What's the difference between food and a meal?
Well...
A meal is made with love, while food is just food?
Yes, that's exactly it.
How does the person, or cat receiving it,
distinguish between food and a meal?
Ritsuko is as beautiful as ever today.
- Could I get a menu?
- Sure thing.
Thank you.
I love you.
You're an idiot.
Welcome...
[Mao Sugimoto]
Long time no see, Takumi.
You're still following him around?
Ren already quit, you know.
- I...
- I'm terribly sorry, miss.
All our seats are currently taken.
I'll come again.
[Hikarigasaki Station]
Here.
Chocolates, for lending me your textbook today.
Thanks.
Here.
Let's split it.
Thanks.
Bon appétit.
My half is bigger than yours.
Looks like it.
I feel my chest squeezing.
It's suffocating,
and makes me tearful.
It's painful, like I've taken a stab to the heart.
The two of us were still strangers a year ago.
Back then, I knew nothing about this feeling in my heart.
Morning.
I knew nothing about it, and yet...
Now my mind is all about Ren.
I'm truly glad my first crush was on someone like him.
Ren, there's a flower petal in your hair.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's still there.
Nope, still there.
Sorry. I was being cheeky.
No, bend down. I'll get it for you.
There.
Thanks.
Ninako, could you get the petals in my hair, too?
What the hell are you doing?
- You asked us for help.
- I wanted Ninako to do it.
Make that clearer next time.
- Dude, seriously?
- You two are totally in sync.
- Are not.
You've got a petal in your hair too, Kinoshita.
Again.
Come on, let's leave the dunce behind.
Who are you calling a dunce?
That's another reason to like him just a bit more.
[Epilogue]
[Winter, One Year Ago]
- There's my name!
- Mine too!
We both made it in!
Ando?
Looks like we're attending the same school again.
Yeah. I bet you're real happy to see me, right?
Huh? Why would I be?
Yes, I made it in!
Mom? Yeah, I made it in.
Yes, I'm in!
Dude, who are you?
Smells like spring.